Guide to the Lucy Monroe Calhoun Family Photographs and Papers, 1886-1993 and undated, bulk 1911-1933 RL.11103
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lucy Monroe Calhoun family photographs and papers
1886-1993 and undated
1911-1933
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Calhoun, Lucy Monroe, 1865-1950
RL.11103
6.3 Linear Feet
The Lucy Monroe Calhoun family photographs and papers contains loose photographs, a photograph album, Lucy Monroe Calhoun's writings and papers, along with Monroe family papers. The photographs include 740 loose black-and-white photographs, generally developing-out paper or gelatin sliver prints, as well as 7 negatives, and one slide, all featuring images of Lucy's residences, locations in a and around Peking (Beijing), and locations elsewhere in China, Cambodia, Japan, and the Philippines between 1910 and 1932. A subset of 15 photographs contains images captured during the Peking riots of 1912. The photograph album (60 pages) contains 94 albumen prints featuring images taken during the Calhoun party's travel between China and the United States in 1911, via Siberia. The Lucy Monroe Calhoun papers series features primarily Calhoun's writings, including her 276-page memoir of her life in China (1910-1936), five typescript articles on China, as well as her letters to family members, commercial postcards, and printed material. The Monroe family papers include mainly writing by family members, from letters to autobiographical and biographical pieces, along with some photographs, postcards, and a few newspaper clippings. There are also extensive letters written by Polly Root Collier and Henry Stanton Monroe, Lucy Monroe Calhoun's niece and nephew, both of whom wrote letters to family members during their stays in China. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Photographs, Photograph album, Lucy Monroe Calhoun papers, and Monroe family papers.
Biographical / Historical
Lucy Monroe Calhoun was born in 1865 to Henry Stanton Monroe and Martha Mitchell; she was the sister of poet and editor Harriet (Stone) Monroe. She became a freelance art critic for Chicago and national newspapers, and served as an editorial reader for the Herbert S. Stone publishing company (1898-1905). In 1904, she married William James Calhoun, who was appointed U.S. minister to China by William Howard Taft, a position he held from 1909-1913. Following her husband's death in 1916, Calhoun served in with the American Red Cross in France. In the 1920s Calhoun returned to China, established her home in an ancient temple, collected art, and became the unofficial "First Lady" of the diplomatic corps in Peking. She remained there until the Japanese occupation of Peking in 1937. She returned to the United States in 1941, and died in Chicago in 1950, at age 85.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Lucy Monroe Calhoun family photographs and papers, 1886-1973 and undated, bulk 1911-1933 were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2014-2016.
Collection Overview
The Lucy Monroe Calhoun family photographs and papers contains loose photographs, a photograph album, Lucy Monroe Calhoun's writings and papers, along with Monroe family papers. The photographs include 740 loose black-and-white photographs, generally developing-out paper or gelatin sliver prints, as well as 7 negatives, and one slide, all featuring images of Lucy's residences, locations in a and around Peking (Beijing), and locations elsewhere in China, Cambodia, Japan, and the Philippines between 1910 and 1932. A subset of 15 photographs contains images captured during the Peking riots of 1912. The photograph album (60 pages) contains 94 albumen prints featuring images taken during the Calhoun party's travel between China and the United States in 1911, via Siberia. The Lucy Monroe Calhoun papers series features primarily Calhoun's writings, including her 276-page memoir of her life in China (1910-1936), five typescript articles on China, as well as her letters to family members, commercial postcards, and printed material. The Monroe family papers include mainly writing by family members, from letters to autobiographical and biographical pieces, along with some photographs, postcards, and a few newspaper clippings. There are also extensive letters written by Polly Root Collier and Henry Stanton Monroe, Lucy Monroe Calhoun's niece and nephew, both of whom wrote letters to family members during their stays in China. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts.
Photography -- China; Riots -- China -- History -- 20th century; China -- History -- Qing dynasty, 1644-1912; China -- History -- Qing dynasty, 1644-1912 -- Pictorial works; China -- History -- Republic, 1912-1949.; China -- History -- Republic, 1912-1949 -- Pictorial works; Cambodia -- Pictorial works; Japan -- Pictorial works; Philippines -- Pictorial works; developing-out paper; Gelatin silver prints; Negatives (photographs); Black-and-white slides; Photograph albums; Memoirs; Postcards; Monroe Family; Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Calhoun, Lucy Monroe, 1865-1950
- Developing out paper and gelatin silver photographs, 1900-1941 and undated; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Series includes 745 black-and-white photographs, dated 1900-1941 (most dates were assigned rather than provided), and ranging in size from 2.25 x 3.25 in. to 9.75 x 7.75 in., with the majority 4.75 x 6.75 in. There are also 7 negatives and one slide present. Staff sorted the images according to location, except for the presentation photographs, where the original order of the photographs was maintained. Images feature Lucy's residences, both in the American legation quarters and her "Temple house;" locations in and around Beijing; as well as other locations in China, Japan, Cambodia, and the Philippines. A subset of 15 photographs contains images captured during the Peking riots of 1912. There is also a folder of images of the Calhoun's that were taken in the United States.
  Lucy Calhoun signed the backs of many of her photographs, but not all, and she often trimmed her photographs to 6.5x 4.5 in. and added a border in black. Eighty-seven of Calhoun's photographs were placed on mounts, and were stored in two Chinese boxes for presentation. Other than by the presence of Calhoun's markings, however, identifying the photographer for an individual photograph is difficult. Some photographs have been folded in half, a few have been hand-colored, and several have letters written on the back.
  - Lucy's residences, 1910-1929; 1
    - Corner of the salon, with bolsters on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-001)
      Title (Chinese)
      沙龙一角，炕椅上放着靠枕
      Image caption
      [no known title]
      Note
      Negative of RL11103-P-053.2.
    - South end of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-003)
      陈列室南面
      Negative of RL11103-P-061.2.
    - View of Legation Quarter street with horse and cart traffic, 1910s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-001)
      使馆区街道上的马车和骑马人
      Legation street
    - View of the American residence in the Legation quarter, 1910s; 6 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-002)
      美国公使馆区内的住宅
      The house we live in, the Legation, Peking
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun leaving the Legation residence in a horse-drawn carriage, 1910s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-003)
      露西·门罗·嘉乐恒坐马车离开公使馆
      L.M.C. starting out
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun standing at the top of the steps outside the Legation residence, 1910s; 3.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-004)
      露西·门罗·嘉乐恒站在使馆住宅前的台阶上
      Lucy Calhoun, Peking, Legation
    - Drawing room in the American Legation residence, March 1911; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-005)
      美国公使馆住宅里的会客室
      March 1911, the drawing room, Peking
    - William J. Calhoun working in the library at the American Legation residence, March 1911; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-006)
      威廉·J.·嘉乐恒在公使馆住宅里的图书室工作
      Taken in March 1911, Peking, The Library
    - Polly Root seated, in profile, holding Chinese doll, 1911; 6.25 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-007)
      波莉·鲁特坐着，手拿一个中国玩偶
      Polly Root, China, 1911
    - Polly Root seated, facing camera, 1911; 4.75 x 6.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-008.1)
      波莉·鲁特坐着，面向镜头
      Polly in Peking
    - Polly Root seated, facing camera, 1911; 4.75 x 6.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-008.2)
      Polly Root, China 1911
      Copy of RL11103-P-008.1.
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun seated on a sofa at the American Legation residence, 1910s; 5.75 x 7.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-009)
      美国公使馆住宅里露西·门罗·嘉乐恒坐在沙发上
      LMC
      Colorized photograph. Top of photograph shows wearing.
    - Women, seated and standing, at lunch with two Manchu ladies, 1910s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-010)
      两位满族妇女和几位外国女士
      A lunch with two Manchu ladies. Alice Peck, B. de Mencol, Polly, Mrs. Liggett, Mrs. Tenkey
    - Lucy and William J. Calhoun standing in front of the American Legation residence, March 1911; 3.75 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-011)
      露西和威廉·嘉乐恒站在美国公使馆住宅前
      Peking, March 1911, to Anna from far-away Lucy Calhoun
      Mount caption
      K. Y. Thompson
    - Exterior and entrance to 10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-012)
      马大人胡同10号院的大门和外面
      Peking, 10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung (formerly Tien Hon Kung) Exterior & entrance, walls & tiles gray, doors red. Ann in her[?] rickshaw.
    - Lucy Calhoun on steps of her living room, 1920s; 4.25 x 3.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-013)
      露西·嘉乐恒站在会客室外的台阶台阶上
      Lucy Calhoun on steps to living room, 10 Ma Ta Jen Hutung
    - Main courtyard, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-014.1)
      中心院子
      These were taken by Hartung at Mrs. Liggett's request
    - Main courtyard, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-014.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-014.1.
    - Main courtyard, showing the study and the "dragon trees", 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-015)
      中心院子，书房，院中的龙形树
      Peking, July 4, 10 Ma Ta Jen Hutung. Main courtyard, showing the study and the "dragon trees"
    - Main courtyard, showing the living room. Dining room at right., 1923 July 11; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-016)
      中心院子，会客室，右面的餐厅
      Peking, July 11, 1923, 10 Ma Ta Jen Hutung, Main Courtyard, showing the living room. Dining room at right.
    - Main courtyard, showing Lucy's room and the "dragon trees", 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-017)
      中心院子，露西的卧室，院中的龙形树
      Peking, July 4, 10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung. Main courtyard showing LC's room and the "dragon trees"
    - Chrysanthemums in the main courtyard, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-018.1)
      中心院子里的各种盆栽菊花
    - Chrysanthemums in the main courtyard, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-018.2)
      Chrysanthemums in court
      Version of RL11103-P-018.1.
    - Dog near large tree in main courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-019.1)
      中心院子里大树附近的小狗
      Photograph has black border.
    - Dog near large tree in main courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-019.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-019.1.
    - Dog near large tree in main courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-019.3)
      Version of RL11103-P-019.1.
    - Dog near large tree in main courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-019.4)
    - Dog near large tree in main courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-019.5)
    - Dog near large tree in main courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-019.6)
      versiion of RL11103-P-019.1.
    - Sun striking tree in courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-020.1)
      太阳照在院中的树上
    - Sun striking tree in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-020.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-020.1.
    - Sun striking tree in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-020.3)
    - Sun striking tree in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-020.4)
    - Plantings in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-021.1)
      院子里的几个盆栽
    - Plantings in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-021.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-021.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Plantings in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-021.3)
    - Plantings in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-021.4)
      Version of RL11103-P-021.1.
    - Tree and plantings in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-022.1)
      院子里的树木和盆栽
    - Tree and plantings in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-022.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-022.1.
    - The ginko tree in the East courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-023)
      东跨院里的银杏树
      Peking, July 4, 10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung. East courtyard. The ginko tree.
    - Snow in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-024.1)
      院中积雪
    - Snow in courtyard, 1932 January 3; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-024.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-024.1. Letter on back of photograph is p. 2 of letter begun on RL11103-P-025.2. "curfew, we went on to the hotel and danced. We saw the New Year in at the Wagons-Sits as guests of Mr. Wowark, but the crwod went to the other hotel so it was rather dull. On New Year's Day we had a lilvely tiffin in the salon. In the afternoon the Johnsons were at home, and Jane had asked me to receive with her. I was touched. All the world came of course, and with the marine band it was very gay. We are dining there tomorrow night. Nelson was glad to have seen you in Shanghai. Many thanks for your cable. I had a huge Christmas mail which arrived just in time, and another at New Year's. I wonder if you are in Arizona, With my love, Lucy"
    - Snow in East courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-025.1)
      东跨院中的积雪
    - Snow in East courtyard, 1932 January 3; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-025.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-025.1. "January 3, 1932. Here is the corner of your East Court, Anna darling, under another aspect. This was taken during the heavy snow of December 21st, which gave us the most beautiful white Christmas that ever you [saw.] Clear skies and brilliant moonlight on Christmas Eve, with red lanterns in the Court, made the house a Carnival. The dinner was very gay. The Johnsons came and the Newells and the Wortons, and after dinner we had blind musicians in the salon. Quite lovely this music was, and everyone liked it. Then we had a hamper of foolish gifts which took well. As there was no midnight mass at the Pietang because of the" The letter is continued on RL11103-P-024.2.
    - Polly Root Collier seated in the courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-026)
      波莉·鲁特坐在院中的椅子上
      10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung. PRC
    - Lucy's dogs beside the marble lion in the courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-027.1)
      露西的两只狗卧在院中的小石狮子旁
    - Lucy's dogs beside the marble lion in the courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-027.2)
      Peiking China, 10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung. Stone lions in the Main Court. (1 lion unseen. 2 Laassa dogs.) Taken by Lucy Calhoun
      Version of RL11103-P-027.1.
    - Lucy's dogs beside the marble lion in the courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-027.3)
      Ting-eih & Pai-Hua
      Copy of RL11103-P-027.1.
    - Amah and Litze in the courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-028)
      保姆和利兹在院子里
      Amah & Litze in court
    - Lucy's dogs at the entrance to her house, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-029)
      露西的两只狗卧在屋门口
    - Two servants at entrance to Lucy's house, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-030)
      两名男仆站在露西屋门口
    - Courtyard seating area, 1920s; 3.25 x 4 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-031.1)
      院中坐着休憩的地方
    - Courtyard seating area, 1920s; 3.25 x 4 in. (Box 1, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-031.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-031.1.
    - The gallery, from the living room, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-032)
      陈列室（从会客室看）
      Peking, July 10, 10 Ma Ta-Jen Hutung. The Gallery from the living room.
    - Left side of living room, facing gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-033.1)
      会客室，左边朝向陈列室
    - Left side of living room, facing gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-033.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-033.1.
    - Left side of living room, facing gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-033.3)
      Version of RL11103-P-033.2.
    - Right side of living room. Gallery at left, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-034.1)
      会客室，右边朝向陈列室
    - Right side of living room. Gallery at left, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-034.2)
      Lucy's house after her return
      Version of RL11103-P-034.1.
    - Left side of living room, with blooming plants, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-035.1)
      会客室左边，开花的盆栽
    - Left side of living room, with blooming plants, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-035.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-035.1.
    - Left side of living room, with mums, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-036.1)
      会客室左边，盛开的盆栽菊花
    - Left side of living room, with mums, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-036.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-036.1.
    - Lucy seated in left side of living room, looking down, 1920s; 3.5 x 2.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-037)
      露西坐在会客室左边的沙发上，低着头
    - Lucy seated in left side of living room, looking up, 1920s; 4 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-038)
      露西坐在会客室左边的沙发上，抬着头
    - Right side of living room at Lucy's house, with mums, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-039.1)
      露西家会客室右边，盛开的盆栽菊花
    - Right side of living room at Lucy's house, with mums, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-039.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-039.1.
    - Right side of living room at Lucy's house, with mums, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-039.3)
    - Right side of living room at Lucy's house, with flowering plants, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-040.1)
      露西家会客室右边，盛开的盆栽花
    - Right side of living room at Lucy's house, with flowering plants, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-040.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-040.1.
    - Right side of living room, with Polly Root Collier [?] seated in corner, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-041.1)
      会客室右边，波莉·鲁特·科利尔[？]坐在一角
    - Right side of living room, with Polly Root Collier [?] seated in corner, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-041.2)
      Ma Ta-Jen Hutung. Aunt Lucy's house.
      Copy of RL11103-P-041.1.
    - Right side of living room, with sun on flowers, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-042)
      露西家会客室右边，太阳照着盆栽花
    - Right side of living room, with female visitor seated in chair, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-043)
      会客室右边，一位女客人坐在椅子上
    - Detail of plant in living room, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-044)
      盆栽植物放大
    - Living room looking toward gallery, with large plant on the coffee table, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-045.1)
      会客室，镂花壁后是陈列室，中间的咖啡桌上放着一个大盆栽
    - Living room looking toward gallery, with large plant on the coffee table, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-045.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-045.1.
    - Living room looking toward gallery, with large plant on the coffee table, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-045.3)
    - Living room looking toward gallery, with large plant on the coffee table, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-045.4)
      Version of RL11103-P-045.1.
    - Living room facing gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-046.1)
      会客室，镂花壁后是陈列室
      Living room facing gallery.
    - Living room facing gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-046.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-046.1.
    - Ann Carrère seated in the living room, looking through to the gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-047)
      安·卡雷尔坐在会客室，镂花壁后是陈列室
      Peking. The living room, looking through to the gallery. Gold bench and grille. Horn laterns. Ann Carrère
    - Lucy Calhoun seated in the living room, looking through to the gallery, 1920s; 4 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-048.1)
      露西·嘉乐恒坐在会客室，镂花壁后是陈列室
    - Lucy Calhoun seated in the living room, looking through to the gallery, 1920s; 3.75 x 2.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-048.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-048.1.
    - The living room, showing entrance to the gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-049)
      会客室，一边通向陈列室
      Peking. The living room, showing entrance to the gallery.
    - Sung jar in the salon., 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-050.1)
      沙龙摆放的宋代瓷瓶
      Peking. The salon. Dull gold screen and table. Sung jar. You see the effect from the gallery.
    - Sung jar in the salon., 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-050.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-050.1.
    - The salon, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-051.1)
      沙龙
    - The salon, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-051.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-051.1.
    - The salon, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-051.3)
      Version of RL11103-P-051.1.
    - Other end of the salon, showing k'ang and iron pictures, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-052)
      沙龙一边，中间是炕椅，后面是铁画
      The salon. Dull gold k'ang and iron pictures. Black fur rug.
    - Corner of the salon, with bolsters on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-053.1)
    - Corner of the salon, with bolsters on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-053.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-053.1.
    - Corner of the salon, with bolsters on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-053.3)
    - Corner of the salon, with bolsters on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-053.4)
      Version of RL11103-P-053.3.
    - Corner of the salon, with bolsters on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-053.5)
    - Corner of salon, with fur on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-054.1)
      沙龙一角，炕椅上放着皮垫
    - Corner of salon, with fur on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-054.2)
      Salon.